gogetfunding.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy - GoGetFunding | GoGetFunding

### **Your Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. We never have and never will sell your information.

This policy has been created to better protect your privacy. This page explains our online information practices, our legal basis for doing so and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

By using the Services offered by GoGetFunding, you’re acknowledging you have agreed to our [Terms of Use](https://gogetfunding.com/terms-and-conditions/) and that you have read and understood this Privacy Policy.

### **Changes to This Policy**

We may update this Policy from time to time. If we do, we’ll let you know about any material changes, either by notifying you on the Site or by sending you an email. If you keep using GoGetFunding after a change, that means you accept this Policy.

### **What We Collect and Receive**

In order for you to create an account on GoGetFunding and use our Services, we need to collect and process certain information. Depending on your use of the Services, that may include:

  * Information you provide by completing forms on GoGetFunding — your name, email, country of residence, login, and password details. We may ask for this information if you register as a user of the Services, subscribe to our newsletter, upload or submit content through GoGetFunding, or if you contact us;
  * Information you provide for identity verification purposes when launching a campaign, including your legal name, business name and Tax ID for business entities, and date of birth;
  * In some cases, our payment processor will request that you provide a secure upload of an identity document (such as your passport, drivers license or other government-issued ID). This is to comply with Know-Your-Client (KYC) anti-money laundering regulations. Depending on the payment processor being enabled, this may be be uploaded via the payment processors website (for example, in the case of Stripe & PayPal). However, we may embed the payment processors verification upload forms on GoGetFunding (in the case of WePay & MangoPay) for your convenience. Verification documents are not seen by and do not reach GoGetFunding’s servers.
  * Details of any requests or transactions you make through the Services. GoGetFunding partners with other companies (such as Stripe, PayPal, WePay & MangoPay) for payment processing, and the payment information you submit is collected and used by them in accordance with their privacy policies;
  * Information about your activity on and interaction with GoGetFunding (such as your IP address, the type of device or browser you use, and your actions on the Site);
  * Information about the ways people visit and interact with our Site, in the form of traffic analytics. You can opt out of being included in Google Analytics[ here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).
  * Communications you send to us (for example, when you ask for support, send us questions or comments, or report a problem);
  * Information that you submit on or to GoGetFunding in the form of comments, contributions to discussions, or messages to other users;

You may decline to provide us with your information. However, this will limit your ability to register for an account or use our Services.

Depending on a campaign’s settings, you may contribute to a campaign by not providing any personal information. You would just need to provide payment details to the payment processor that has been enabled on a particular campaign.

### **How We Use This Information**

We use the information we collect for the following purposes:

  * To keep your account secure and protect our Services (including to verify the identities of campaign owners and prevent fraud and abuse);
  * To enable us to provide you with our Services, and to improve and promote our Services;
  * To create and administer your account, contact you, and customize your experience on GoGetFunding (for example, to show you campaigns in your country); and
  * To track and analyze use of the Services so that we can improve how GoGetFunding is performing and provide users with the best experience possible.

### **European Union Users** ****

Data protection law in Europe requires a “lawful basis” for collecting and retaining personal information from citizens or residents of the European Economic Area. Our lawful bases include:

  * Performing the contract we have with you: In certain circumstances, we need your personal data to comply with our contractual obligation to deliver the Services, enable campaign owners to create and display their campaigns, and enable donors to find and make donations to them.
  * Legal compliance: Sometimes the law says we need to collect and use your data. For example, to comply with anti-money-laundering regulations we need to collect certain information.
  * Legitimate interests: This is a technical term in data protection law which essentially means we have a good and fair reason to use your data and we do so in ways which do not hurt your interests and rights. We sometimes require your data to pursue our legitimate interests in a way that might reasonably be expected as part of running our business and that does not materially impact your rights, freedom or interests.For example, we use identity, device, and location information to prevent fraud and abuse and to keep the Services secure. We may also send you promotional communications about our Services, subject to your right to control whether we do so. We analyze how users interact with our Site so we can understand better what elements of the design are working well and which are not working so well. This allows us to improve and develop the quality of the online experience we offer all our users.

### **How This Information Is Shared**

**Information that’s shared publicly** ****

When you create an account, we create a basic public profile page for you on GoGetFunding, containing your name, the date the account was created, and a list of campaigns you have donated to, launched or are following. If you provide the information, your profile will also show your picture, about text and location.

The name you provide appears with your donation, the comments you post and messages you send on GoGetFunding. People can click your name to view your profile.

If you would like to have a profile, but don’t want others to see your name or profile image, you may choose an account image or name that is not identifiable. You can modify or delete certain information associated with your account (such as your profile image, about text and location) from your [user profile](https://gogetfunding.com/edit-user-profile/).

If you are a campaign owner, we require that you use your real name.

**Information that isn’t shared publicly**

The following data will not be publicly displayed or revealed to other users:

  * Any payment information you provide;
  * Your email address;
  * Your password details;
  * Your IP address;
  * Your phone number;
  * Your date of birth and other identity verification documentation (for campaign owners);
  * Communications you send to us (for example, when you ask for support, send us questions or comments, or report a problem).

**Information that’s shared with trusted third-party services**

We may share your information with certain trusted third-party services to help us provide, improve, promote, or protect GoGetFunding’s Services (like when we partner with payment processors). When we share data with third-party services that support our delivery of the GoGetFunding Services, we require that they use your information only for the purposes we’ve authorized, and that they protect your personal information at least to the same standards we do. We may also share information that’s aggregated and anonymized in a way that it doesn’t directly identify you.

**Information that’s shared with campaign owners & team members**

When you back a campaign, the campaign creator will know your name, the amount you have donated, any reward you have selected, your email address, payment method, and any shipping information – if provided. Campaign owners never receive a donor’s credit card details or other sensitive payment information.

Campaign owners are required to keep donor information confidential, except as strictly necessary to communicate with donors directly. Campaign owners should not ask for personal information that isn’t necessary to provide your reward, and should never request sensitive personal information such as your Social Security number or payment information. Contact us at info@gogetfunding.com if you receive a request for information that seems inappropriate or excessive.

Team members are third parties that campaign owners can appoint to help manage their campaign. These team members may be able to access the information available to campaign owners (including donor’s names, email addresses, donation amounts, reward selections, and are required to treat donors personal information with the same care and respect as campaign owners are.

**Information that’s shared to protect GoGetFunding and comply with the law**

We reserve the right to disclose personal information when we believe that doing so is reasonably necessary to comply with the law or law enforcement, to prevent fraud or abuse, or to protect GoGetFunding’s legal rights, property, or the safety of GoGetFunding, its employees, users, or others.

**Links to other websites and services**

Our Site may include links to other websites or services whose privacy practices may differ from GoGetFunding’s. When you use a link to an external site or service, the privacy policy and data processing disclosures for that site or service governs.

### **Retention**

We will retain your information as long as your account is active, as necessary to provide you with the Services or as otherwise set forth in this Policy. We will also retain and use this information as necessary for the purposes set out in this Policy and to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, enforce our agreements and protect GoGetFunding’s legal rights.

We also collect and maintain aggregated, anonymized or pseudonymized information which we may retain indefinitely to protect the safety and security of our Site, improve our Services or comply with legal obligations.

### **Your Rights**

Users residing in certain countries, including the EU, are afforded certain rights regarding their personal information. Except where an exception or exemption applies, these rights include the ability to access, correct, and request deletion of your personal information. While these rights are not applicable globally, all GoGetFunding users can manage their personal information, as further described below, in their [account settings](https://gogetfunding.com/edit-user-profile/).

You can request a downloadable copy of your personal data from GoGetFunding [upon request](https://gogetfunding.com/contactus/). To modify or delete the personal information you’ve provided to us, please log in and update your profile. We may retain certain information as required by law or as necessary for our legitimate business purposes.

### **Email Notifications**

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. We try to keep emails to a minimum and give you the ability to opt in to any marketing communications we send.

We will send you email relating to your transactions on GoGetFunding. You may also elect to receive certain marketing email communications, in accordance with your preferences, and from which you may opt out at any time by adjusting your [notification settings](https://gogetfunding.com/user-email-notifications/).

We’ll also send you service-related announcements when it’s necessary to do so.

### **Security**

We take security seriously, and the security of your personal data is important to us. We follow industry-standard practices to protect the data we collect and maintain, including using Transport Layer Security (TLS) to encrypt information as it travels over the internet. No method of transmission over the internet or electronic storage is completely secure, so GoGetFunding cannot guarantee its absolute security. Your account information is protected by a password, which you should choose carefully and keep secure.

We encourage the responsible disclosure of vulnerabilities of our Services by emailing info@gogetfunding.com.

### **Data Protection Authority**

Subject to applicable law, if you are a citizen or resident of the European Economic Area, you also have the right to (i) object to GoGetFunding’s use of your personal information and (ii) lodge a complaint with your local data protection authority or the United Kingdom Information Commissioner’s Office, which is GoGetFunding’s lead supervisory authority in the European Union.

United Kingdom Information Commissioner’s Office

Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire

SK9 5AF, United Kingdom

Telephone: +0303 123 1113

Fax: 01625 524510

Web: https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/

### **Children**

People under 18 (or the legal age in your jurisdiction) are not permitted to use GoGetFunding on their own. GoGetFunding does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 and children under 13 are not permitted to register for an account or use our Services.

If you believe that a child has provided us with personal information, please contact us at info@gogetfunding.com. If we become aware that a child under age 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information, we’ll delete it.

### **Cookies**

GoGetFunding uses cookies and these other technologies to help recognize you as a repeat visitor and, to improve the quality of our Services.

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

### **Questions?**

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of GoGetFunding then you may[ contact us](https://gogetfunding.com/contactus).

_Updated: May 2018_
